The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Junior, hurry up !
This old man's survival
depends on you !
Go !
Country of Zhao
Corpse Sect
Tiandao Sect
Wufeng Valley
Tianshui City
Wang Family Village
Heng Yue Sect
Teng Family City
Xuan Dao Sect
Piaomiao Sect
Heaven's Tower
Corpse Sect
Country of Zhao
Where are you from ?
A rank 2 country.
I'm Li San from the sect's branch in the country of Lu.
I'm here for the promotion test.
18th cave on the right.
Understood.
Looks like a Senior is coming.
Greetings, Ancestor !
I am Wang Lin.
Please inform Ancestor Ye Zizai
that I have urgent matters to discuss.
Who activated our Corpse Sect's formation for you ?
Greetings, Ancestor Ye !
Ye Zizai
Corpse Sect Ancestor
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Thank you for delivering the message, Junior Wang Lin.
I'm aware of Junior Brother Wu Yu's situation.
Since he requested,
would you like to join our Corpse Sect ?
Since I'm here,
I could use this chance to cultivate.
Disciple agrees.
Since you're fated with Junior Brother Wu Yu,
then you are his disciple.
From now on,
you're a core disciple of the Corpse Sect.
I will take care of Adai.
Since he was a friend of Junior Brother Wu Yu,
then I'll personally take him as my disciple.
Dismissed.
He knows Wu Yu is in danger
but doesn't seem worried by it.
I think Wu Yu
trusted the wrong person.
Junior Mu Rong
pays respects to Uncle.
Mu Rong
Corpse Sect Elder
Late stage
Foundation Establishment
You're an Elder,
no need for formalities.
Ancestor Ye arranged a cultivation cave for you.
Let me guide you there.
Uncle, focus on cultivation.
Once you reach Middle stage Foundation Establishment,
use the Corpse Sect's cultivation method you were given
and then you can come out.
Grade 10
Earth Yin
A grade 10 Earth Yin spot !
Wu Yu didn't lie.
This place is perfect for the Underworld Ascension Method.
Luo Sha
Ye Zizai's Corpse Puppet
Late stage Nascent Soul
Your Junior Brother left too early.
He left before Lord Zi's Divine Sense awakened.
Foolishly, he asked you for help,
setting himself up for a trap !
Now that we know where he is,
let's hurry and help Lord Zi devour Wu Yu !
Luo Sha, you haven't finished devouring me yet.
Don't order me around.
Back then, you were so proud when
the both of you obtained me and Lord Zi
as your Corpse Puppets.
But you never imagined that
these Corpse Puppets were already seeded with our Divine Sense.
Your entire Corpse Sect
is just a market selling bodies for cultivators that lost their body.
Adai's body is excellent,
you should try possessing him.
How will you deal with that brat
named Wang Lin ?
No worries.
The Foreign Battlefield cleanup is about to start.
We will receive our token in a few days.
Once the Cultivation Alliance's envoy opens the portal
I only need to absorb 3 breaths of spiritual energy
to finish my possession.
He's here !
Why did it gain 2 leaf symbols ?
Could there be wood element energy here?
Save me...
This is the reason
the Corpse Sect is an extreme Yin energy gathering spot.
Save me... Save me...
His cultivation is above Nascent Soul !
Save me...
Senior, Junior is not powerful enough to h...
Save me !
Heaven's Tower
Country of Zhao
It's already been 500 years...
If not for our Huangquan Sect
taking a liking to Zhao,
the Cultivation Alliance wouldn't have built Heaven's Tower here.
And you guys would never have entered the Foreign Battlefield.
Don't forget, you're still my Corpse Puppet.
Lord Envoy,
Ye Zizai of the Corpse Sect pays respects.
No need for formalities, Ye Zizai.
We're old acquaintances.
Lin Yi
Heaven's Tower Envoy
Early stage Soul Formation
In just a few years
your Corpse Puppet has reached Late stage Nascent Soul !
You flatter me, Envoy.
How could the Joyful Union Sect miss this event ?
Piao Nanzi of the Xuan Dao Sect
greets fellow cultivators.
Chen Huan
Founder of the Joyful Union Sect
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Chen Yan
Founder of the Joyful Union Sect
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Piao Nanzi...
I heard you destroyed the Heng Yue Sect.
Is it true ?
It is true.
All of the Heng Yue Sect Ancestors are dead.
Piao Nanzi, you just took advantage of their weakness.
Did fellow cultivators covet Heng Yue Mountain too ?
It's a pity I was faster than you.
You...
Wu Qinfeng
Wufeng Valley Ancestor
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Gao Qiming
Piao Miao Sect Ancestor
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Yun Mei
Tiandao Sect Ancestor
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Zhi Yi
Tiandao Sect Ancestor
Middle stage Nascent Soul
All the Nascent Soul cultivators of Zhao are here.
Greetings, Lord Envoy.
Everyone...
this once in 500 years opportunity
will soon begin.
The country of Zhao is responsible
Note: 1 li = 150m
for clearing 100 000 squared li at 58 degrees north of the entrance.
All the high-grade artifacts collected
will belong to your respective sects.
Lord Envoy,
how will the battle of Jue Ming Valley proceed ?
The rules of the Cultivation Alliance
say that only 3 sects from Zhao may enter.
So this battle between you is inevitable.
Same old rules:
only Foundation Establishment disciples may fight.
Nascent Soul and Core Formation cultivators
cannot intervene.
Such a terrifying pressure !
Is this Soul Transformation ?
My Nascent Soul can't endure this !
Lin Yi, envoy of a rank 5 cultivation country
welcomes the Envoy of the Cultivation Alliance.
Envoy of the Cultivation Alliance
Giant Demon Clan member
Late stage Soul Formation
The spiritual energy here is trash.
It's not even worth breathing.
This is an envoy from the Giant Demon Clan !
Is this the power of the Giant Demon Clan ?
Envoy, why did the Alliance send you ?
Is there something wrong ?
Pay attention to these words.
In 3 months,
the gate will open.
If any of you
happens to find a bead like this,
you must give it to me.
If you hand it over,
you will be rewarded with a Soul Transformation artifact.
But if you dare to hide it from me...
I will destroy your country of Zhao
and kill all of you !
Lin Yi, I'm taking your 7-colored lotus artifact.
I'll be waiting for the good news.
In the Jue Ming Valley battle
there will be 7 jade tokens.
At least 4 must be crushed.
We will meet at the entrance of the valley in 7 days.
The sects that have a token
are allowed to enter the valley.
We follow your orders.
Wait a minute, fellow cultivator Qiming.
I have a request for you.
Uncle,
the Ancestor summoned all Foundation Establishment disciples to Cave 36.
I'm here to accompany you.
Lead the way.
Finally, I get to kill people !
It's the perfect chance to cultivate my Corpse Puppet.
Weird...
Aside from Mu Rong at Late stage
all the others just reached Foundation Establishment.
Ancestor.
The battle of Jue Ming Valley is critical.
You are the Corpse Sect's finest disciples.
You must fight hard to keep our sect's token.
In Jue Ming Valley,
you will follow Mu Rong's lead.
Here is our sect's token.
I accept.
Everyone's Soul Blood
was already collected in these jades
except for one person...
Will he dare to refuse ?
With my Nascent Soul cultivation, I can kill him instantly.
As expected, he's trying to trick me.
Sorry Junior Brother Wu Yu...
I won't save you
nor let him send word of this.
After entering Jue Ming Valley,
you will follow the plan.
Remember: if you kill 5 enemies,
I will give your Soul Blood back.
Those who try to flee
even just a thousand li
will have their Soul Blood crushed.
You can go.
Show those righteous cultivators
the might of our Corpse Sect.
I planted a Divine Sense curse on him
but some mysterious entity erased it.
I searched for days
but found no trace of him.
Fellow cultivator Teng,
my divination showed me that he will be
in Jue Ming Valley.
Why do you want to find his family ?
Enough, fellow cultivator Teng.
Settle the score with the culprit.
Why would you attack innocents ?
Innocents ?
My Li'er was the Teng Family's
most gifted Junior with exceptional talent !
Now that he's dead,
who will answer for it !?
But if word of this gets out,
it will ruin both our reputations !
Fellow cultivator Qiming,
As long as you agree to help me,
this Soul Formation artifact, the Spirit Tortoise armor,
will be yours.
Jue Ming Valley
Country of Zhao
I must get the jade with my Soul Blood.
It should be doable with my cultivation.
What do we do now, Elder Mu Rong ?
Mu Rong, act now.
We must seize Wang Lin's body.
I must thank you all
for contributing to the Jue Ming battle.
Elder Mu Rong ?
Elder, what are you doing ?!
No, my Soul Blood !
You're dead !
The Corpse Puppets are waking up,
be careful !
What is this purple mist !?
All their puppets rebelled.
Uncle, save me !
You reap
what you sow.
Country ranks are granted by the Cultivation Alliance. They correspond to the highest level cultivator there is in that specific country.
rank 1 = Foundation Establishment
rank 2 = Core Formation
rank 3 = Nascent Soul
rank 4 = Soul Formation
rank 5 = Soul Transformation
rank 6 = Ascendant
Rank 6 countries are given a planet by the Cultivation Alliance and they manage rank 5 countries. Rank 5 countries manage rank 4 countries and so on and so forth.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?